<welcome-pack>
    <title>Welcome to Digital Publishing</title>
    <sections>
        <section>
            <p>
                We’re looking forward to meeting you. We’ll invite you to our Slack team before you start, so you don’t need to wait to get to know us :) you can join before your first day if you want to, but don’t feel like you have to.
            </p>
            <p>
                We hope this guide answers most of the questions you might have about your first few weeks, but if you want to know anything else you can email your new line manager.
            </p>
            <p>
                The traffic around our office can be unpredictable, so don’t worry if you’re a bit late, just let us know if possible. And so you know for your first day, there’s not really a dress code - you can wear anything you’re comfortable in as long as it’s not offensive.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>What to expect on day one</title>
            <p>
                We know the first day in a new job can be tough - we’ll try to make it as easy as we can, but let us know if there’s anything we can do to help!
            </p>
            <p>
                When you arrive at ONS you’ll need to stop at the security gate. They should be expecting you - if you’re driving they’ll tell you where you can park. You’ll then sign in at reception and collect your temporary pass - you might need to have your photo taken.
            </p>
            <p>
                Let us know on Slack that you’ve arrived and one of your team will meet you. If you can’t access Slack, or haven’t joined yet, you can ask reception to let us know.
            </p>
            <p>
                We’ll introduce you to the rest of your team (the ones who are in that early!), show you your desk and locker, and go through some basic information about the office (toilets, kitchen, fire exits - that sort of stuff).
            </p>
            <p>
                Once you’ve settled in you’ll go for a coffee with your line manager. It’ll probably take around an hour, and you’ll find out more about your role, how you fit into the organisation, and a bit about our plans for the next couple of years.
            </p>
            <p>
                When you get back, your team will have finished the morning stand-up and should be back at their desks. Talk to your new team, get to know them and find out what they’re working on. Ask your team about anything you’re interested in.
            </p>
            <p>
                If you want to go to the shop, coffee shop or canteen, just let us know and we’ll show you the way.
            </p>
            <p>
                At lunchtime you’ll go for lunch with your team! There’s no rush to be back, so make the most of the opportunity to get to know each other.
            </p>
            <p>
                After lunch we’ll take you to collect your laptops - a Windows laptop and a MacBook Pro. You’ll need the Windows laptop to login to Fusion (our HR system). You’ll need to add your bank details so you get paid, but that’s the admin work done for a few days.
            </p>
            <p>
                Next you’ll spend some time with people outside your team. Digital Publishing has lots of interesting and varied roles and you’ll get to find out a bit more about what they do and how your role relates to theirs.
            </p>
            <p>
                We’ll introduce you to our publishing and editorial teams where you’ll observe the work they do and chat to some of them about their role. Most of them use the products you’ll be building, so think of this as your first bit of user research.
            </p>
            <p>
                If we’ve got our paperwork right, you’ll need to have your photo taken at 3pm for your security pass. This should be on your first day but it doesn’t always happen that quickly. Don’t worry if not, you can keep using your temporary pass on your second day.
            </p>
            <p>
                At the end of the day you’ll have a short one-to-one with your line manager. Nothing to worry about, it’s just a chance to discuss how your first day has gone. You’ll probably have loads of questions and we’ll do our best to answer them.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>What to expect on day two</title>
            <p>
                When you arrive on day two you can go straight to your desk. You can start any time after 7am, and we’d like you to be in before our morning stand-up at 10am.  Before the morning stand-up you can begin setting up your development environment on your MacBook Pro. We want you to spend more time talking to people, but there’s likely to be some free time you can use to get things set up.
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll go to the morning stand-up with your team and give your first update. We keep it short, so briefly covering what you did yesterday and what you’re doing today is enough. Sometimes there’ll be a more in-depth discussion or demo after the stand up - we’d recommend joining in if it happens!
            </p>
            <p>
                If anything from the morning stand-up interests you then feel free to chat to people afterwards to find out more. People are sometimes busy or have meetings to get to, so you might need to find another time to get together.
            </p>
            <p>
                After the morning stand-up you’ll get to talk to more people. We’ll introduce you to our product, delivery and interaction design teams. You’ll find out more about how the teams interact, more about their roles, and have the chance to discuss how you might work together.
            </p>
            <p>
                Some of the team go to lunch together in the canteen, while others prefer to eat at their desk. It’s your choice how you spend your lunch, but you’re welcome to join us.
            </p>
            <p>
                After lunch we’ll get one of your team to show you around the office. There’s lots to look at and some of it might need some explanation. Take your time to absorb as much as you can, and feel free to stop to chat to anyone you want - but we’ve just made you talk for a day and a half so we’ll understand if you’d rather spend some time at your desk.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>What to expect for the rest of your first week</title>
            <p>
                When you arrive on day three we’ll dive straight into the technical side of your role. 
            </p>
            <p>
                Depending on when you start, this might be our planning and retrospective day. If it is, you’ll go to a show and tell and your team’s retrospective and planning sessions. That means we’ll get less of the other stuff done today.
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll get a high level overview of the various frontend systems and how they fit together, and we’ll go into more detail on anything you’re interested in - whether that’s how things currently work, what we’re planning on doing, our roadmap for the next few months, or our longer term goals.
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll also find out a bit more about our development lifecycle - like how we use Git, how code reviews work, how to access our test environments, and how we build, test and deploy code to production.
            </p>
            <p>
                After lunch we’ll get some of the boring development environment setup things done - setting up accounts and creating a GPG key for GitHub, just the essentials to let you start contributing.
            </p>
            <p>
                Once that’s done we’ll give you your first task. We’ll keep it simple and introduce you to a few components at a time. It’ll probably be a minor template or style change.
            </p>
            <p>
                You can work at your own pace, so if you’d like to spend a bit of time exploring the codebase and understanding how it fits together you can, and we’ll make sure someone is around to help if you get stuck. We’ll also try to get your work reviewed, signed off, and deployed to production as quickly as possible - your first release!
            </p>
            <p>
                The rest of the week will be similar. We’ll increase the complexity of your tasks and show you more of the frontend architecture. We’ll also send you lots of links to information we’ve got on GitHub, some of the tools you might need (like Kibana for logging, or Concourse for CI), and you’ll get plenty of time to explore them.
            </p>
            <p>
                Some of the Digital Publishing team are based in Titchfield - we’ll try and find time for you to chat to some of them on Skype to find out more about their work.
            </p>
            <p>
                On Friday afternoon you’ll have another short one-to-one with your line manager. You’ll get to discuss how your first week has gone, ask any questions you have, and give us any feedback on your experience so far. We want to make it better for the next person who joins our team, so don’t be afraid to let us know if we get anything wrong.
            </p>
        </section>
        <section>
            <title>What to expect in your second week</title>
            <p>
                We hope you’ll have settled in a bit and got to know most of your team by now.
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll be in the routine of attending daily stand-ups, and you’ll have some tasks you can work through at your own pace. You can pair program with anyone on your team, or ask anyone on your team to pair with you on one of your tasks.
            </p>
            <p>
                We’ll encourage you to find someone in Digital Publishing you haven’t met yet and go for a coffee with them.
            </p>
            <p>
                There might be a bit more boring admin work to do sometime this week, but we’ll try to keep it to a minimum. If you’re eligible, we’ll need to get you security cleared. This is just a form you need to fill out, and you’ve got plenty of time to do it, but it asks for lots of information you probably won’t have immediately available.
            </p>
            <p>
                We’ll make sure you’ve got tasks to work on until the start of the next sprint where you’ll join the rest of your team in planning your own work. Sometime in the first two weeks you’ll also get your first 10% time - this is your opportunity to work on anything that interests you.
            </p>
            <p>
                You’ll also have another one-to-one with your line manager. Together you’ll explore how you work together, your personal development goals, and how your line manager can best support you in your new role. These one-to-ones will become a regular opportunity to review your progress, give each other feedback, and discuss your role, the work, the organisation or anything which might be bothering you.
            </p>
            <p>
                You don’t need to wait for a one-to-one. If anything comes up you can speak to your line manager or ask for a one-to-one at any time.
            </p>
        </section>
    </sections>
</welcome-pack>